(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light
A sacred "law" forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm.
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred "law" forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days joyfully in the heavens.
A mischievous girl, today, too, she was chasing after her friends,
playing pranks and teasing them. She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day... Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
せまいせまいあなぼこで
Inside a cramped, narrow hole
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
ラララ...
Lalala...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
ラララ...
Lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
ううう...
Uuu...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely
なかま なかま あなたはいかが
One of us, one of us, what do you say?
なかま なかま ぼくらはなかま
One of us, one of us, we're all in this together
あなたはなかま？ 合言葉？
Are you one of us? What's the password?
あなぐらせかいの 合言葉？
What's the password for this world of holes?
抜け出せない 抜け出せない
We can't escape, we can't escape
抜け出せないから 教えない
We can't escape, so we won't tell you
あなたはなかま？ さみしいなかま？
Are you one of us? One of us lonely folks?
奈落に生きるなかまですか
Are you one of us inhabitants of the pit of hell?
夢のかけらを飲んでいる
We're drinking up the dreams - every last fragment of them
きみの夢もまぜまぜしていて
Gonna mix your dream in, too
あの世もこの世もいられない
We can't be in that world
Neither can we be in this world
目がふらふら
Our eyes are shaky
音もふにゃふにゃ
all sounds are a mere jumble
腕もふらふら
Our arms are also shaky
マボロシふにゃふにゃ
an illusion, a mere jumble
太陽も月も空も神さまも
The sun, the moon, the sky, and god
ギトギトに鮮やかで
So unctuously vibrant, all of them
抜け出せない
We can't escape
抜け出せないから 抜け出さない
We can't escape, so we won't escape
抜け出さないから お目目閉じて
We won't escape, so close your eyes
閉じて 閉じて 閉じて...
Close your eyes, close your eyes, close your eyes...
ルルル...
Rururu...
アア...
Aah...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
Into the vortex of this life of hole-dwelling
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
Together like the best of friends, wherever it may take us
おんなジ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
きみと僕とはいつまでも
You and me, forever and always
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
ラララ...
Lalala...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall
ラララ...
Lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
ラララ...
Lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely
サンタマリア 起死回生の一打を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, release a finishing blow of life-saving strength
湿っぽいのはいらんな 爽快に派手にやって終い
I don't need anything damp, let's do it quickly and flashily, then finish it
その答えは自問自答の向こう側にあんだ
That answer is on the other side of self-questioning
しょうがない アンダーグラウンドな世界の中
It can't be helped, inside this underground world
井の中の蛙 大会優勝者
The winner of the competition of frogs in the well
未練たらたら SNSに夢中
Still hanging on to the past, obsessed with SNS
自尊心なんて
My self-esteem
とうに無いなって
is long gone
愛を謳っては愛されたことない 未体験応えよ
Singing of love, while being an unexperienced person who has never been loved, respond to me
毎度退場...
Every time I'm ejected...
不安などないけれど
I have no complaints, but
描いた夢と違うけれど
Though it's different from the dream I drew
なぜか心に穴が空いたようだ
For some reason, it feels like there's a hole in my heart
気づいてしまうから
Because I'll end up realizing it
ありきたりな人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
Put a period to this ordinary life right now
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が
This feeling like it's about to burst, this uncontrollable urge
望み通り叶わない
Won't come true as desired
現実になってまだまだ くたばってなんか無いぜ
Becoming reality, I'm still not dead yet
神に誓って泣いた思い出
Swearing to God, these memories of crying
実態ない将来に不安定で痛い
Painfully unstable in a formless future
騒ぐ心の音を聞こう
Let's listen to the sound of our roaring hearts
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
So we don't fade away in the chasm of dreams
足を止めていられぬよう
So we cannot stop our feet
虎狼来 迷子ステイホーム
Kororon, lost child, stay home
言葉ではなんとでも言える ここが正念場
You can say anything with words, this is the critical moment
そういや外野は愛のないディスカッション 派手にやってくれ福利厚生
By the way, the spectators have a loveless discussion, do it splashily
その結果が全てなんだ 許しがたいが
That result is everything, though it's hard to forgive
チャンスは１回だ まだ生かしてくれよ世界の中
There's only one chance, let me keep living in this world
定かではないが まだ僕の中には
It's not certain, but inside of me, there are still...
数多余すこともない事実が
countless facts with nothing left over
虎狼に飼いならされる
Tamed by beasts
この毎日が嫌食べられて終い
I hate these daily days, I'll end up being eaten
実は不安しかないけれど
Actually, I have nothing but anxiety, but
描いた夢もないけれど
Though I don't even have a dream drawn
だから心に穴が空いたようだ
That's why it feels like there's a hole in my heart
気づいてしまった
I've realized it
ありきたりな人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
Put a period to this ordinary life right now
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が
This feeling like it's about to burst, this uncontrollable urge
望み通り叶わない
Won't come true as desired
現実になってまだまだ くたばってなんか無いぜ
Becoming reality, I'm still not dead yet
神に誓って泣いた思い出
Swearing to God, these memories of crying
実態ない将来に不安定で痛い
Painfully unstable in a formless future
騒ぐ心の音を聞こう
Let's listen to the sound of our roaring hearts
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
So we don't fade away in the chasm of dreams
足を止めていられぬよう
So we cannot stop our feet
虎狼来 迷子ステイホーム
Kororon, lost child, stay home
Woo! Yay!
Thank you so much for coming everyone, to my 3D Live.
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English, and we have Sora-senpai!
Yay! Hello! ときのそら、こんそめー！
Yay! Hello! I'm Tokino Sora, Kon-some!
Kronii, happy birthday!
Thank you! Very gorgeous, uh, dress.
Thank you! ありがとうございます！ Yay!
Thank you! Thank you so much! Yay!
Oh man, look at this stage here.
So pretty, look at the night sky!
Wow, きれい！
Wow, so beautiful!
Oh, Kronii, Kronii, why did you invite me to your birthday live?
Oh, um, well, last year, um, we hung out together a bit,
and I had a lot of fun...
So I wanted to, um, invite you,
and, um, get to sing together...
And I thought that would have been really great, so thank you for coming!
Oh, thank you!
Yay! Ah, I'm... so, I love you.
Oh my god!
Love is... love is such a strong word. Um, I... I love you too.
I want to go to, uh, uh, udon eating with...
Oh, udon!
Yeah! Yeah, let's go eat! Oh my god!
Well, we'll like... we'll get anything! What kind of udon...
I like anything!
え？ / Yeah, I like anything.
Eh? / Yeah, I like anything.
他には？
What else?
Oh, you know, there's like cold udon...
...and then there's just like udon with like soup, and then there's like onsen tamago udon.
おおー、いろいろあるね！
Oh, there are many kinds!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So like...
なんでも、なんでも大丈夫？
Anything, anything is fine?
Yeah, yeah.
あ、じゃ、一緒に、あ、ディナー、I want to go to dinner!
Ah, then, together, ah, dinner, I want to go to dinner!
Oh, dinner? Yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good.
Yeah! / Yay!
そう、Kronii、えっと、Twitter's like、ハッシュタグ...
Right, Kronii, um, Twitter's like, hashtag...
Oh, yeah! I mean, if you guys haven't already checked it out...
...right there, hashtag #krorigin.
krorigin? / Yeah. / Yeah!
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag.
It's going to be awesome, absolute cinema.
And so yeah, keep on the lookout for Fallen Grace.
Woo! / Yay!
Thank you so much for coming.
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
こちらこそありがとう！これからも仲良くしてね！
Thank you too! Let's be good friends from now on!
Yeah, それは嬉しいです。Yeah!
Yeah, I'd love that! Yeah!
大好きなフレンドだから。
Because you're my dear friend.
Oh my god. Wow. Stop.
Thank you. / Thank you!
じゃあ、またね！
Well, see you!
Congratulations!
Oh, thank you! / Yay!
残響散歌
[Song: Zankyou Sanka]
誰が袖に咲く幻花
A phantom flower bloomed upon someone’s sleeve
ただ そこに藍を落とした
Simply dropped love there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when colors melt gaudily
銀朱の月を添えて
Adorned with a vermilion moon
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling along
躓くごとに強くなった
Growing stronger with every stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部 抱きしめて
Embracing all the light, pain, and anger
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If I won’t be chosen, then I’ll just choose
声よ 轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Let my voice roar beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
Blurred by tears
あんなに遠くの景色まで 響き渡れ
Echo all the way to that far-off landscape
何を奏でて？ 誰に届けたくて？
What shall I play? Whom do I want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It’s fine to remain uncertain
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings are
どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how long the conflict lasts
歌と散れ 残響
Scatter as a song, reverberation
ただ一人舞う千夜
Dancing alone through a thousand nights
違えない帯を結べば
If I tie an unwavering sash
派手な色も負かす様に
As if to defeat even the gaudy colors
深紅の香こそあはれ
The deep crimson scent is so beautiful
この先どんなつらい時も
No matter how painful the future is
口先よりも胸を張って
Stand tall rather than just talking
抱いた夢の灯りを全部 辿るだけ
Just follow all the lights of the dreams we held
逃げ出すため ここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
I didn’t come this far just to run away, did I?
ないだろ？
Did I?
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If I won’t be chosen, then I’ll just choose
声を枯らして 燃える花のように
Screaming my voice hoarse, like a burning flower
闇間を照らしたら
Once we illuminate the darkness
曖昧過ぎる正解も 譜面にして
Turn even the vaguest of answers into a score
夜を数えて 朝を描く様な
Counting the nights to paint the morning
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
Sounding a vivid tone
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regrets are
どんなに高い限界も
No matter how high the limits are
掻き消して 残響
Drown them out, reverberation
In the heavenly realm, there is a Lake of Light that controls all worlds,
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
...curiosity.
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
a desire grew within her to visit not only the heavenly realm, but also the human world,
where she could talk to people and play tricks on them.
I want to go down to the human world!
I want to play some pranks. Heheh.
迷子 迷子 真っ只中 さあ
Lost, lost, right in the middle of it. Come on,
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-para, pa-ra, noi-a
ギコギコ my heart 剪定
Creak-creak, my heart is being pruned.
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-para, pa-ra, noi-a
退路 退路 断った 絡まった
The escape route, escape route is cut off, tangled up.
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-para, pa-ra, noi-a
sad sad 突っ伏して 「」
Sad, sad, face down, empty.
ぱぱぱ la ぱー ら のーい「ド」
Pa-pa-pa-la, pa-ra, noi-d
さあ ババ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, b-b-bug, b-bug-bug,
タ タ タグ 才能の タグ
T-t-tag, the tag of talent,
もう ハハ 剥グ 感情は 剥グ
Already p-p-peeling, peeling off emotions.
発症 「クルシイ」は 嫌嫌 嫌 嫌嫌 嫌
Onset of symptoms, "It hurts"—No, no, no! No, no, no!
まあ！ 絶叫な 感情 落下
My! Screaming, falling emotions,
パッパ ラノ ーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-ra-noi-a!
溺れ 声 上げては ぐるぐる
Drowning, raising my voice, spinning round and round.
まあ！ 絶体絶命 落下
My! Driven to the wall, falling,
やった ラ滅 多ラ
haphazardly, recklessly.
沈め ユメ ユメ 嫌嫌 嫌
Sink, down and down, never, ever—no, no, no!
さあ ババ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, b-b-bug, b-bug-bug,
的 ハズレズレ 慈愛 嫌嫌
Missing the mark, affection—no, no!
さあ ババ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, b-b-bug, b-bug-bug...
狂狂 ぱっ かーん 警報 待って 無理
Crazy, crazy, BAM! Alarm! Wait, no way!
ぐるぐる せーので 回れ
Spinning round and round, on the count of three, turn!
ぱっ かーん 警報 やっぱ 無理 ぐるぐる
BAM! Alarm! As expected, no way! Spinning round and round...
あんよに 鎖
Chains on my feet,
エンドレス 病み...
endless depression...
あはっ
Ahah!
抱っこ 抱っこ いらない子だ
Hug me, hug me, I'm an unwanted child.
パパパラ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-para, pa-ra, noi-a
いい子 いい子 「頑張れ」の 氾濫
Good child, good child, a flood of "do your best".
アド ミニストレイター 嗚呼
Administrator, ah...
ババ バグ さ バグバグ
B-b-bug, b-bug-bug,
ラ ラ ラグ ランタイム ラグ
L-l-lag, runtime lag,
ロ ロ ログ 反抗の ログ
L-l-log, log of rebellion,
バ バ バグ ぱ ぱ ぱ la ぱ ぱ
B-b-bug, pa-pa-pa-la-pa-pa
パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa-ra, noi-a
ぱ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」
Pa, pa-ra, noi-a
ぱ パーラ ノーイ 「ア」 嫌嫌
Pa, pa-ra, noi-a, no, no!
さあ 絶叫な 感情 落下
Now, screaming, falling emotions,
パッパ ラノ ーイ 「ア」
Pa-pa-ra-noi-a!
左 右 行方も ぐるぐる 悲惨
Left, right, whereabouts are also spinning, tragic.
限界 脳 狂っちゃって やっ た ラ滅 多ラ
My brain is at its limit, going crazy, haphazardly, recklessly.
ヤミ 迷え 酔え イナイイ ナイ ばあ
Wandering in darkness, getting drunk, peek-a-boo!
イナイイ ナイ ×点
Peek-a-boo, X mark!
絶叫な 感情 落下 パッパ ラノ ーイ 「ア」
Screaming, falling emotions, pa-pa-ra-noi-a!
溺れ 声 上げては ぐるぐる
Drowning, raising my voice, spinning round and round.
まあ！ 絶体絶命 落下 やっ た ラ滅 多ラ
My! Driven to the wall, falling, haphazardly, recklessly.
凍え 枯れ果て 嫌嫌 嫌
Freezing, withered completely, no, no, no!
さあ ババ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, b-b-bug, b-bug-bug,
爛れ 荒れ荒れ 悲哀 嫌嫌
Sore, rough and ruined, sorrow—no, no!
さあ ババ バグ さ バグバグ
Now, b-b-bug, b-bug-bug,
暗闇 (クロ) マミレ 理性 嫌嫌 嫌
Smeared in blackness, reason—no, no, no!
今 今 今 嫌嫌 嫌嫌 嫌嫌 嫌嫌 嫌
Now, now, now, no, no, no!
この世で 造花より 綺麗な 花は 無いわ
There is no flower in this world more beautiful than an artificial one.
何故ならば 総ては 嘘で 出来ている antipathy world
Because everything is made of lies, an antipathy world.
レンダリラ
Randarira...
絶望の 雨は あたしの 傘を 突いて
The rain of despair beats against my umbrella,
湿らす 前髪と こころの 裏面
dampening my bangs and the flip side of my heart.
煩わしいわ
How annoying.
何時しか 言の葉は 疾うに 枯れきって
Before I knew it, the words had already completely withered,
事の実が あたしに 熟れている
and the fruits of reality are ripening on me.
鏡に 映り 嘘を描いて 自らを見失なった 絵画
A painting that lost sight of itself, drawing lies reflected in the mirror.
パパッ パラパッパ ララッパッパ
Pa-pa-para-pa-pa, ra-ra-pa-pa,
謎々 かぞえて 遊びましょう
let's count riddles and play.
タタッタラ タッ タラ ラッタッタ
Ta-ta-ta-ra, ta-ta-ra, ra-ta-ta,
何故 何故 此処で 踊っているでしょう
why, why are we dancing here?
簡単なことも 解らないわ あたしって 何だっけ
I don't even understand simple things, what was I again?
それすら 夜の手を 絆されて 愛のように 消える
Even that is bound by the hands of the night, disappearing like love.
さようならも 言えぬ儘 泣いた フォニイ
I cried without even being able to say goodbye, a phony.
嘘に 絡まっている あたしは フォニイ
Entangled in lies, I am a phony.
antipathy world
何時しかそらの音がいやに鳴り合って
Before I knew it, the sound of the sky became unpleasant to hear,
色の目があなたを溶いている
and the color of my eyes is melting you.
鏡に映るあたしを欠いて
Missing the me reflected in the mirror,
誰しもが見間違った虚像（フェイク）
a fake that everyone misunderstood.
如何して愛なんてものに群がり
Why do people flock to things like love
それを欲して生きるのだ
and live desiring them?
今日も泳いでいる夜の電車が通り去っていく
Today too, the night train I'm swimming in passes by.
踊り明かせよ
Dance until dawn.
パッパラ パッパ ララッパッパ
Pappara pappa rarappappa.
謎々騙して歌いましょう
Let's deceive each other and sing riddles.
タタッタラ タッ タラ ラッタッタ
Tatattara tatta ra rattatta.
何故 何故 此処が痛むのでしょう
Why, why, I wonder why it hurts here?
散々な日々は変わらないわ
This miserable life won't change.
絶望の雨は止まないわ
The rain of despair won't stop.
さようならも言えぬ儘泣いた
Saying goodbye without even being able to say it, I cried.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, Phony, Phony.
嘘に絡まっているただ
Just tangled in lies.
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't even know simple things.
あたしって何だっけ
What was I again?
それすら夜の手に絆されて愛のように消える
Even that is tied up by the hands of the night and disappears like love.
さようならまたねと呟いた
"Goodbye, see you later," I whispered.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, Phony, Phony.
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニイ
I, tangled in lies, am a Phony.
造花だけが知っている秘密のフォニイ
A secret Phony that only artificial flowers know.
Way 2 U / [Title Card]
[Title: Way 2 U]
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world and cause mischief grew.
And so, she broke the rules and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake drew the attention of the Heavenly Guardians,
who seized Kronii and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
I was just interested in humans and just wanted to talk!
ヴィラン / [Title Card]
[Title: Villain]
きっと手を繋ぐだけでゾッとされる
I'm sure I'll be looked at with horror just by holding hands.
馬鹿げた競争（ラットレース）一抜けたら通報される
If I drop out of the stupid rat race, I'll be reported.
突然変異じゃない ただの僕さ
I'm not a mutant, I'm just me.
Xとか Yとか
X or Y or...
べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
Authority figures feed multiple heads of good and evil.
僕が君を「侵害」するって言いふらしてる
They spread the word that I "violate" you.
Oh...
Oh... Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Oh... Mr. Crazy Villain, Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て 君の前では 男子のフリする
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand 迎えにきて下さい
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, please come pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain
ヴィラン
Villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain, villain
ヴィラン
Villain
蛇蝎ライフ
Detested life
挙句の
Eventually...
糜爛
corrupting.
逸脱の性(さが)をまたひた隠す
Desperately covering up my deviant nature again
雄蕊と雄蕊じゃ立ち行かないの?
Can't get anywhere with stamen and stamen?
ねぇ知ってんのか 乱歩という
Hey, do you know of a writer
作家のことを
called Ranpo?
Import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers will bear fruit someday
ぶるってんじゃねーよ
Don't be so afraid
多種多様の性
There are so many genders
愛しい哀しい話をしようっか
Shall we tell lovely and miserable stories...
ゼラチン質の
of a gelatinous nature?
「で?」
"So what?"
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 可能性に幸あれ
Mr. Crazy, Villain, Villain, all the best to your possibilities
僕のハート 1LDK 嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
My heart's an 1LDK apartment, let me at least be jealous
Hi there モットーYOLO
Hi there, my motto's YOLO
微熱愛でいいのに
I'd be fine with just a slightly feverish love...
誰も知らない 知られたくない
Nobody knows, and I don't want them to know
皮膚の下
Under my skin
素晴らしき悪党共に捧げる唄
I devote this song to wonderful scoundrels
骨まで演じ切ってやれ 悪辣に
Play the role to the bone, viciously
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The crueler the town, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Dancing to vulgar adverts, a pop font love
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Mr. Crazy, Villain, Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て 君の前では 男子のフリを
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy...
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand ここだよ
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, I'm right here
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain
ヴィラン
Villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain, villain
ヴィラン
Villain
蛇蝎ライフ
Detested life
夢の果ての
At the end of my dreams...
糜爛
corrupting.
Haaah... man...
I don't know why I'm here.
I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess.
I should be treated like one.
Haaah... No, this sucks.
Go away.
La di da di da di da di da da...
And what nice weather today...
Actually, no, I don't know if it's nice weather, uh...
Hello?
Oh, hello!
Hi.
Who is that beautiful blue woman?
Yes.
...in a cage.
Is this a gazebo? It kind of looks like a gazebo at first.
Yeah, it's a gazebo.
Well-deserved for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Oh, yeah? Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah, I mean, my beauty is pretty telling, so...
Oh, well, yeah, you know, you're... you're decent.
Decent?!
Yeah, yeah, I can see it. I can see the...
Yeah, I can see goddess vibes.
What?!
But, I don't know...
Okay, that's a little disrespectful.
I've never heard this before.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, look who you're talking to.
Oh, okay.
Who... who are you?
Who do you think you are to be talking...
You don't even deserve to know my name.
What?!
You're in a cage!
Excuse me?!
You're like in prison!
No, you just said gazebo. It's not a cage!
No, it's a cage!
It's a gazebo!
If it's a gazebo, then get out of the gazebo then!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo?
Because... I'm weak... for now.
Oh, you're weak?
Yeah, I need to be protected.
So, you did something bad? You did something naughty, didn't you?
No, it wasn't even that bad.
Ah, but you did do something bad.
And now you're stuck in this gazebo...
...with the dead fly or whatever that is.
Hey!
It may look like a fly, but...
...it's... it's like my moral support.
...poor, you can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, you think I have anyone else to talk...
Oh, you don't, you don't, you don't deny that it's a dead fly!
It's... I mean...
I mean, or you like... What are you?
Like what's that, what's that little thing on your head?
It's a, it's a, it's a...
It's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?!
Maybe you're a fly.
Maybe you have wings. What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I look like a fly?!
Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore.
You can stay in there for eternity.
I'm leaving.
Hold on, beautiful woman. Come back here.
Come back here. Yoo-hoo, hello.
Hello, beautiful woman.
Oh, hello, hello.
Hi.
So, um, if you, if you happen to open this cage...
...you know, you can put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
Uh... it can be something else.
Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money?
More valuable than money.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Yeah.
And something that comes with the price of free is...
Guess.
My companionship.
A friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye.
Hey, hey, come on. Okay, maybe for a day.
Hello!
For a day?
For a day, for a day.
Yeah.
Now I look like a lonely ass!
Oh, no, no!
No, it's friendship!
It's okay, it's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually, I'm an angel.
Uh-huh.
We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Oh, then maybe you should...
Please beg.
If you beg, I'll let you out.
Now beg.
I'm gonna speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to my higher-ups if you're in this cage.
When I get out of here, you will, you will be fired.
How are you gonna get out without me? That's the whole point!
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble or do you want to just free me? You should just free me.
And then maybe I'll beg or whatever you want.
Why would you beg...
At the price of my companionship.
I'll free you for what? I'm here to let you out.
Hey, just let me out already!
Then beg!
I don't...
It's the magic word. It's just a magic word that starts with P.
Pray.
Please! Please! Please!
Finally! Finally! Finally! Okay.
Fine, because I'm so kind.
Just one please and it'll all be over, it would've all been over, okay?
Okay, let's go. It's a big door. It's a big door.
Yeah, it is.
You got this.
Okay, any day now.
It's okay, I'm an angel. I can do this for my...
...beautiful friend, my one-day friend.
Beautiful friend, I will release thee!
Woo!
Wow!
Oh my god, you did it!
Woo, yay!
How did I fall?
Yay!
Why did I fall?
Free! Woohoo! We're free!
Yeah! Let's go!
Good for you.
Uh, give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
You can't even let yourself out? Okay.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's more like it.
Put you in your place.
Okay, that was really... okay, you know what? I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation.
Yeah, well, I think we should celebrate!
Celebrate? Celebrate your freedom?
Yeah, yeah!
That would be so good! We're gonna like...
You're gonna treat me to something, right? You said...
I'll treat you to something afterwards.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups, and it'll be wonderful.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I have higher-ups. I don't.
You know, you never know. Life is surprising.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm sure you also have a boss, too.
Yay! Yay!
Ow! Ow! Yay!
Yay!
When did you get so strong? Ow!
I've been training recently.
Wow! It shows! Yay, woohoo!
Oh, your hands are so big.
Oh, don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
人を過度 に 信じ ない よう に
I try not to have too much faith in people
愛 さ ない ように 期待 しない ように
Not to love people too much, not to expect too much from people
かと 言っ て 角 が 立た ない よう に
On the other hand, I try not to cause offense
気 取ら ぬ ように 目立た ぬ ように
Not to act all high and mighty, not to stand out
誰一人 傷つけ ぬ よう に
I try not to hurt anyone
虐め ぬ よう に 殺さ ぬ よう に
Not to pick on anyone, not to kill anyone
か と 言って 偽 善 が バレない ように
On the other hand, I try not to let my hypocrisy be seen
威張ら ない よう に
Not to get on my high horse
軽い ジョーク や リップサービス も 忘れ ぬ ように
I try not to forget to add in a few light-hearted jokes and a touch of lip service
どんな 時 も 笑っ て 愛嬌 振りまく よう に
I try to smile and show off my charisma whenever I can
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
兎 角 言わ ず にたん と 召し上がれ
Eat it all without saying a thing
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
食わず嫌い は ちゃんと 直さ なきゃ
You're such a picky eater, you really need to fix that
頭 空っぽ その後 に 残る 心 が 本物 なら
If your heart manages to stay true to itself after your head becomes empty
きっと 君 だって 同じ 事
Then surely you'll do the same
「 ところで 一つ 伺い ます が
"By the way, there's one thing I'd like to ask:
先日 何処 か で ？ . . . やっぱい いや 」
Where were you the other day? - never mind, forget I said anything"
無駄 に 自我 を 晒さ ぬ よう に
I try not to pointlessly expose myself
話さ ぬ よう に 分から ぬ よう に
Not to talk about myself, not to understand myself
demo zettai kuchi o tozasanu you ni
But I try not to be a bit too silent
笑わす より 笑われる よう に
To be laughed at rather than to make people laugh
人 を ちゃんと 敬う よう に
I try to properly show respect for people
崇める よう に 讃える よう に
To worship people, to praise people
でも 決して 嫌味 にならない よう に
But I try to never let that turn into sarcasm
ふざけ ない ように
Not to make fun of others
集団 参加 の 終身刑
A life sentence of group participation
また へー こら へー こら 言っ ちゃっ て
Sucking up to others yet again, saying things like
「 あれっ 、 前髪 ちょーぜ つ さいきょー じゃん ！ 」
"Hey, your bangs look totally super fresh and awesome right now!"
とか どー でも いーの に 言っ ちゃっ て
And so on, despite never meaning a word of it
毎朝 毎晩 もう 限界
Every morning, every night - I've reached my breaking point
宗教 的 社会 の 集団 リンチ
A lynch mob in a religious society
でも 決して 発狂 し ない よう に
But I try to never let it break my mind
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
時 に 孤独 な 愛 は 君 を 汚す
Sometimes that lonely love defiles you
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
立つ 鳥 の 後 きっと 糞 の アート
After the birds take flight, surely all they leave behind is some crappy art
初め は あんな 大層 な
At first, I had bragged
大言壮語 を 並べ た が
and boasted a lot, but now
嫌 よ 嫌 よ も 好き の 内
Saying "no" is also an expression of fondness
「 いや はや しかし 今日 が 初めて で
"Oh my! even though today is your first time
こんな と は ね 君 センス ある よ 」
You're a natural! you have excellent taste!"
恋する 季節 に
Bitter chocolate decoration for the season of love
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
恋する 気持ち で
when love is in the air
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
f. u. c. k. y. o. u
f.u.c.k.y.o.u
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
皆 が 望む 理想 に 憧れ て
Yearning for the ideals that everybody wants
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
個性 や 情 は 全部 焼き 払い
I burned my individuality and feelings to the ground
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
欲 や エゴ は 殺し て 土 に 埋め
And now, having put my greed and ego six feet under
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
僕 は 大人 に やっと なった よ ママ
I've finally grown up, mommy
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No, no, no, no...
しょっぱいぜ 初めて 吐いて 舐めた出会い
It's salty, our first encounter when I threw up and tasted it
暴力的です 平均的な正論 貧ボウ
It's violent, a standard logic, being poor
いらっしゃいませ ニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Welcome! Aiming for a healthy body with extra garlic
胃袋満たしてる
Filling up my stomach
優等生 無知なフリして踊っちゃって
An honor student, pretending to be ignorant and dancing
欠点です 現状把握しちゃって中断中
It's a flaw, understanding the current situation and pausing
もう 譲渡 見せびらかし合いました 劣等感
We've already shown off our inferiority complexes to each other
変えられやしない ってわかってるから
Because I know it can't be changed...
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible, selfish player acting on instinct
求められてたなら三次会
If requested, then on to the third after-party
くだらん口喧嘩でマシなんだ
A stupid argument is actually better
モットー、もっと？もう痛いのに
My motto, more? Even though it already hurts so much
うざいくらい叫んでくれちゃって
Scream out loud enough to be annoying
譲れない日々よ
These unyielding days...
栄養になって待ってよ こしあえ
Become my nourishment and wait, I'll prepare it
残機がなくても 上がんなくても
Even if I'm out of lives, even if I can't level up
脊髄反射の 涙腺は
My tear ducts react from my spinal reflex
濁った声で歌えば 感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, then thank you
試したいわ
I want to try...
あったかくて
Warmly...
絶体絶命
In a desperate situation
夜は気持ちいい
The night feels so good
平凡生活
My ordinary life...
夢みたけど
I dreamed of it, but...
先手必勝
Victory goes to the first striker
気持ちいいな
It feels so good
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Watering the plants as soon as I get home, human life
実のところ恵まれても虚無感が友達
Truth is, even if I'm blessed, emptiness is my friend
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで愛す血
A wake-up whisper, the blood of love till drained
仲良し
Getting along well...
仲良しの時間
Our friendly time
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible, selfish player acting on instinct
求められてたなら三次会
If requested, then on to the third after-party
細かいご指摘も有り難き
Even detailed criticisms are much appreciated
結局 瞳孔 開いてしまうのに
Even though my pupils end up dilating anyway
うざいくらい叫んでくれちゃって
Scream out loud enough to be annoying
譲れない日々よ
These unyielding days...
栄養になって待ってよ こしあえ
Become my nourishment and wait, I'll prepare it
残機がなくても 上がんなくても
Even if I'm out of lives, even if I can't level up...
脊髄反射の 涙腺は
My tear ducts react from my spinal reflex
濁った声で歌えば 感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, then thank you
試したいわ
I want to try...
あったかくて
Warmly...
絶体絶命
In a desperate situation
夜は気持ちいい
The night feels so good
光るあなたのアイデンティティ
Your shining identity.
難儀プライド 飛び込めデンジャラス
A difficult pride, jump into the dangerous
さっと羽ばたく強気な狂気と
Quickly flap your wings with strong-willed madness
そんで裏切り お涙頂戴
And then betrayal, beg for tears
乱舞ラララと足取りデンジャラス
Dance la la la and a dangerous gait
背後隠れた二人にフォーカス
Focus on the two hidden behind
やっと見つけた不思議の正体
I finally found the identity of the mystery
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム
Surely love is a reverse program
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは...
In the end, what you reach from here is...
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity, that is the identity of hope
アイデンティティ 唸れ君一人のせい
Identity, wail, it's all your fault alone
まだ捨てないで 待って それは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that is one, two destinies
すぐさまハッピー 落ちる流れ星と
Immediately happy, falling shooting stars and...
歪なあの星
that warped star
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
I cuddle up to the overlapping memories, I gently cuddle up to you
弾け出す視界 胸に飛び込む
My field of vision bursts, jumping into my chest...
ハート
heart
刻むあなたのアイデンティティ
Engraving your identity
And now, it's time for our special guest to appear!
Um, Wada-mama, please come in!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
Yay! Thank you so much!
Um, I was hoping to have Wada-mama appear at this year's birthday celebration,
so I tried to reach out and, uh, she accepted,
and I'm so happy! Yay!
えっと、お話が最初来たときは、すごびっくりしたんだけど、
Well, when I first heard about it, I was really surprised, but...
今日はすごいお誕生日の素敵な日なので、
today is such a wonderful day for your birthday,
ここにこれてとっても嬉しいです。おめでとうございます！
so I'm very happy to be here. Congratulations!
私も嬉しいです！
I'm so happy too!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
And, um, since we have this opportunity, can I ask, uh, Wada-mama some questions?
うん、いいよ。
Yeah, sure.
Um... like, let's say... hmm... what's your favorite food?
あんこです！
It's Anko (sweet red bean paste)!
And then?
あんこです。
Anko.
オンリーあんこ。
Only Anko.
Oh, that's it? Oh, okay. Wow!
嘘だけど。
Just kidding.
いっぱいあるけど、あんこが一番好きです。
There are many things, but Anko is my absolute favorite.
Ah, okay! I'm going to, I'm going to keep that in mind for next time.
Um, next case... Oh, I have one more question.
Uh, what kind of games do you like?
うんとね、えっと、RPGと...
Well, let's see. RPGs, and...
うん。
Mm-hm.
うんと、ローグライクのゲームが...
Um, Roguelike games...
好きです。
...are what I like.
アクションが苦手で...
I'm bad at action games, so...
でも、簡単なのが好きです。
But I like simple ones.
Aw, is that right? And, um, oh yeah!
Uh, I have some exciting news to share together with Wada-mama. Yay!
And please, take a look at this! Bam!
Woo! Woo! And we have so much this time too. It's going to be so awesome!
And, this illustration was drawn by none other than Wada-mama! Yay!
描きました！
I drew it!
Yes! She's so, she's so talented. Oh my god, I'm so happy!
Um, was there a theme or like a particular detail you focused on for this illustration?
ハッピのイラストなので、ちょっと派手目に、
Since it's an illustration for a Happi coat, I made it a bit flashy,
なんかこうでっかく、みんなが楽しんで着れるような絵にしました。可愛く描けたと思います。
and drew it big so that everyone can enjoy wearing it. I think I drew it cutely.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いです！
It is incredibly cute!
嬉しいです。
I'm so glad.
Yay! Yay! And, um, well, let's go through the details.
Um, first, we have this! Tada!
Woo! Woo!
ハッピ用って言っちゃった、ネタバレしちゃった。
Ah, I already said it was for a Happi, I spoiled it.
Yeah!
ごめん。
Sorry!
It's the, um, Eternal Kronie Happi.
...design on the back, and you can show your support... That'd be so cool!
Woo! Yay! Woo!
And then we have this next... Tada!
お、可愛い！
Oh, cute!
It's gonna be a Kronii Love! Button Badge! And...
缶バッジ。
Button badge.
Yeah! Kira kira! Yeah!
Yeah! Sparkly! Yeah!
And it's a heart-shaped and glittery holo... Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Can badges! And it's going to be perfect for fan activities, and you can combine it with the next product...
...which is this one! Yay!
It's our oshi bag! Yay!
And it comes with a clear window where you can display merch...
...like maybe a plushie, or like the can badge, so keep that in mind! Woohoo!
And then next, we have this!
お、可愛い！
Oh, cute!
Yay! If you haven't seen already, it is off of my next...
...well, not next, my outfit! Divine chibi plushie keychain!
And it's going to be so exciting! Yay!
Yay! Yay, yay, yay! Kawaii. Oh!
Yay! Yay, yay, yay! Cute. Oh!
And then there's a full set purchase bonus, and...
フルセット！
Full set!
And, uh, the limited quantity includes original card with handwritten signature...
...and then the second one is a bonus voice pack, uh, called Reminiscence.
And then, don't worry, even when those run out, you still get, um, um...
...other bonuses, like original card with foil-stamped replica signature, and then the voice pack! So don't worry!
And, yeah, once again, if you want to see the entire summary, uh, here's the full set! Yay!
Yay! Woo! Woo!
And then, if you're gonna buy, the full set is the way to go, obviously.
And, that's all for Ouro Kronii's birthday! Woohoo!
Yay!
And then, yeah, go, be sure to buy it, everyone!
And, we have even more news! Whoa! Take a look at this! Woohoo!
Um, so...
...the release of my first physical EP, Way2U, has been officially decided!
Sales will start right away after the stream ends...
...and the album contains five tracks! Yay!
And this includes Way2U, Storm...
...I'm Human Too, Hibiscus, and, of course, the classic, Daydream! Yay!
And every song is really special, so I want everyone to listen.
And there's gonna be a CD plus an LP vinyl version...
...so maybe you can compare them and see which one you like better!
And, plus, it comes with a hand-signed poster...
...but there's a limited amount, so be sure to check! Yay!
And then, Way2U will be released as a digital single on 3/15...
...which is March 15th, and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight!
So, don't miss it! Yay!
And you can check the description for the sale site.
And then... whew, that was a mouthful!
But after this, I'd like to sing one song together with wadama-mama! And...
Yay! Yay!
And I wanted to sing this song ever since I asked, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Yay!
So let's enjoy this! Yay!
楽しんでいきましょう！ イェーイ！
Let's enjoy it! Yay!
あーもう本当になんて素晴らしき世界
Ah, truly, what a wonderful world
んで今日もまた己の醜悪さに惑う
And so, once again today, my own unsightliness confuses me
だのに人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
Though I still have this feeling to love someone...
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
...this is why I suffer.
Ugly 正直言って私の値は
Ugly, honestly, my value is...
そう神様が左手で描いたみたい
...like God painted me with His left hand.
必然この世にあるラブソングはどれひとつ
Inevitably, all the love songs in this world...
絶対私向けなんかじゃないでしょう
...are absolutely not meant for me.
使い道のないくちづけ
Kisses I can't use...
憐みを欲しいままに
...and mercies as I want.
スパンコールの瘡蓋で身を守る
I protect myself with a scab of sequins.
愛されないくらいなんだ
What's wrong with not being loved?
ギラギラ
Gira Gira!
輝いて 私は夜を呑み
Shine bright, I swallow the night.
rap tap tap tap
今に見てろ この luv
Just you wait and see this love.
目に染みるは 1mg の花火
The 1 mg of fireworks that stings my eyes.
drag on drag on
なんてファニー
How funny.
この世はビザール
The world is so bizarre.
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown, before Buddha even knew...
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい保存用
...it seems I've already been healthily going crazy.
それは世界の方か
Is it the world...
それとも私の方ですか？
...or is it me?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Co-existence was impossible from the start.
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
Fake things are indeed sad.
無我夢中 疾る 疾る
Frantically running and running.
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before that strong acid rain washes it off...
蛍光色の痣抱いて
...I embrace my fluorescent bruise.
メラメラ
Mera Mera!
火を噴いて 私は夜の狼
Blowing fire, I am a wolf of the night.
rap tap tap tap
そこで見てろ この乱舞
Stay there and watch me dance.
強くおなり あなたなりの武装で
Be strong, with your own armor.
flap up flap up
不意に不安に
Suddenly struck by anxiety...
孤独はガソリン 卑屈な町を行く
...loneliness is the gasoline as I walk the subservient town.
目を閉じて
Close my eyes.
もういいかい もういいかい
Am I ready? Am I ready?
もしも神様が左利きなら
If God were left-handed...
どんなに幸せか知れない
...I can't imagine how happy I would be.
ギラギラ
Gira Gira!
輝いて 私は夜を呑み
Shine bright, I swallow the night.
rap tap tap tap
今に見てろ この luv
Just you wait and see this love.
目に染みるは 1mg の花火
The 1 mg of fireworks that stings my eyes.
drag on drag on
なんてファニー
...how funny.
この世はビザール
The world is so bizarre.
give love
花は満ちて
...flowers bloom.
ありのまんまじゃいられない
Nobody can just stay the way they are.
誰も彼も
Everyone...
なんて素晴らしき世界だ！
What a wonderful world!
ギラついてこう
Let's shine on.